<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Srikar Durgam</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Srikar Durgam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Pizza Reviews</title>
      <link>/post/analyzing-pizza-rating/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/analyzing-pizza-rating/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to another blog, this week I will be analyzing pizza reviews, this data again comes from tidytuesday project. I am very excited to visualize some of this data. I have never worked with geographical data and I want to possibly add a map to this blog(You’ll find out if I was successful or not.). I am also a huge fan of Dave Portnoy’s show reviewing pizza, the idea behind this show is basically that he takes ONE SINGLE BITE of a pizza joint’s cheese pizza and rates on a scale of 1 to 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the best show of all time: The Office</title>
      <link>/post/analyzing-the-best-show-of-all-time-the-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/analyzing-the-best-show-of-all-time-the-office/</guid>
      <description>In this post I will be analyzing a popular American show called The Office. The Office aired from March 2005 to May 2013. It has a total of 9 seasons and 201 shows and all streaming now on Netflix. A note to all hardcore office fans the entire library is going to leave the netflix platform in Jan 2021 and will make its debut on NBC’s own streaming platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 First Presidential Debate Analysis</title>
      <link>/post/first-presidetial-debate-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/first-presidetial-debate-analysis/</guid>
      <description>My first blog post! If you don’t know me already, hello! My name is Srikar. I am a data analyst for an ISP in Atlanta, GA and currently in the middle of getting my business analytics and data science masters degree from Wake Forest.
The purpose of this blog post isn’t to nudge you in one way or another, but only to provide an analytical view of what the candidates are saying.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
